

Craig Tanaka Mudzingwa

Web Developer

About Me

I am a Web Developer currently studying Computer Science at the University of Namibia and employed as the Senior Web Developer at 'Divine Web Graphix & Web Designs'.

I am someone who loves learning and although my main area of expertise is Web, I do dabble in mobile and pc apps.

Contacts

Address : 53 Steedman Rd, Athlone, Gweru, Zimbabwe

Phone: +263 782 408 958

Email: tanxyrogue@gmail.com

craig-tanaka.web.app

github.com/craig-tanaka

inkedin.com/in/craigtanaka/

Expertise

UX Design

Website / Webapp Development

Backend & Frontend Management

Search Engine Optimization

Project Management

Experience

Senior Web Developer

Divine Graphix & Web Designs | Aug 2019 - Ongoing | Handel Street, Windhoek West, Namibia

Recieved client requirements for website and used them to develop a mockup designs. Apon mockup approval setup domain, hosting and wordpress installation for project. Created and edited wordpress themes and plugins to match design requirements.

Freelance Web Developer

Self Employed | Aug 2018 - Ongoing | 53 Steedman Rd, Athlone, Gweru, Zimbabwe

Designed UX based on client requirements. Developed websites and webapps based on accepted UX design. Set up backend and hosting for said apps. Managed hosting servers for deployed apps.

Education

Bsc Computer Science (Hons)

University Of Namibia 2017 - 2019

Mobile Web Specialist

Google Africa Developer Scholarship 2020

Skills

Wordpress Sites, Themes & Plugins Development

HTML, CSS & Javascript

NodeJs

Firebase Stack

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD

Awards

2018

Best 2nd Year In Computer Science

University Of Namibia

2018

Best Student Object Oriented Programming

University Of Namibia